# Robbie Boyd

Flash Developer, Auckland, New Zealand

#### Contact:

Email: Robbie.c.boyd@gmail.com

**Skype:** t000flash **Phone:** +64 21 774 352

LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/in/t000flash

Portfolio: <a href="http://www.cargocollective.com/robbieboyd">http://www.cargocollective.com/robbieboyd</a>

#### **About**

Flash developer from Auckland, New Zealand. I have various digital work experiences in both agencies and working as a freelancer. Interested in new job opportunities internationally and work in an environment which is pushing the boundaries in Flash/Interactive. I have 5 years work experience varying between Full/Part-time and contract website development.

I am keen to learn new skills and have always had great feedback from work peers about my work. I learn quickly and enjoy having experienced developers around to both 'sponge' from and bounce ideas towards.

I think I bring a fun and hardworking ethic to the work place. I really enjoy trying new things, whether it is digital or real. I am a fan of sports, tattooing, beaches, Flash Player 10.2 (that looks too rad).

View my CargoCollective portfolio for a more detailed portfolio <a href="http://www.cargocollective.com/robbieboyd">http://www.cargocollective.com/robbieboyd</a>. Referees and code sample are available on request.

#### **Experience**

**SKULL AND BONES** Auckland, New Zealand

http://www.skullandbones.co.nz

Flash developer October 2009 – Present

**Lead Flash developer** building websites/micro-sites, Facebook applications, interactive DVDs, web banners. SKULL AND BONES works as both an agency supplier and also client direct.

Clients: BNZ (Bank of New Zealand), Steinlager, Colenso BBDO, Tribal DDB, Tequila/TBWA/Shift.

**Skills:** Actionscript 3, Actionscript 2 (for web banners), Facebook (Javascript) API using AS3 ExternalInterface to communicate

AIM Proximity BBDO

Auckland, New Zealand

http://www.aimproximity.co.nz

Website developer June 2008 – October 2009

**Website developer** building websites/micro-sites, Facebook applications, web banners, HTML

Clients: Vodafone New Zealand, Air New Zealand, TVNZ.co.nz, Fonterra, Visa Entertainment

**Skills:** HTML, CSS, Javascript, Flash AS3/AS2, PHP, Facebook (Javascript) API using AS3 ExternalInterface to communicate

Vodafone NZ Auckland, New Zealand

http://www.vodafone.co.nz Website administrator/developer October 2006 – July 2007

Website administrator/developer working and maintaining Vodafone NZs website and intranet.

Skills: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Basic content management skills

## Giltrap City Toyota

Auckland, New Zealand http://www.gct.co.nz Website administrator

October 2005 – October 2006 (part time roll)

**Website administrator** managing the Giltrap City Toyota website. This involved photographing all new cars and adding the photos and car details to the online database.

#### **Freelance**

Clickthrough NZ Pure

http://www.winwithnzpure.co.nz

Flash development October 2010

**Touchpoint** Various jobs

2007

**Brave New World** 

Various jobs 2007

## **Education**

## Media Design School:

July 2007 – May 2008 Diploma in Digital Media

# Skills

Programming Languages	Programs
Actionscript 3	Adobe Flash
Actionscript 2	Adobe Dreamweaver
HTML	Adobe Photoshop
CSS	Adobe Fireworks
Javascript	Adobe Illustrator
XML	FlashDevelop with Flex SDK
PHP (Basic)	Subversion
XSLT (Basic)	Microsoft Office
	Microsoft OS (Prefered)